A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- California, 1932-1990; 205; 4.8 Cubic Feet; 12 __Boxes __4.8 cubic feet
  - California - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 205.D
    - University of California - Marine Biochemistry - (Fox, Denis L.), 1944, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - University of California - Marine Biochemistry - (Fox, Denis L.), 1944, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - University of California - Marine Biochemistry - (Fox, Denis L.), 1944, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - University of California - Virus Research - (Equipment, Wendell M. Stanley), 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - University of California - Virus Research - (Equipment, Wendell M. Stanley), 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - California - Humanities and Arts, 205.R
    - Mills College - Far Eastern Music - (Chi-Fang Li), 1949-1951 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Occidental College - Regional Studies, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Occidental College - Regional Studies, 1951-1959 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Occidental College - Regional Studies, 1951-1959 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Occidental College - Regional Studies, 1951-1959 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Occidental College - Regional History - Southwest Conference Proceedings, 1950-1951, 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Occidental College - Regional History - Southwest Conference Proceedings, 1950-1951, 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Stanford University - Hoover Institute - (Slavic Studies), 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Stanford University - Hoover Institute - (Slavic Studies), 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Stanford University - Hoover Institute - (Slavic Studies), 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Stanford University - Stegner, Wallace - (Far Eastern Literature), 1949-1954 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Stanford University - Stegner, Wallace - (Far Eastern Literature), 1949-1954 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Stanford University - Stegner, Wallace - (Far Eastern Literature), 1949-1954 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - University of California - Korean Studies - Books (For Library), 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - University of California - Latin American Studies - King, James F. - (Abolition of Slavery), 1949-1952 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - University of California - Slavic Studies - (Personnel Development), 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - University of California - Slavic Studies - (Personnel Development), 1949-1956 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - University of California - Slavic Studies - (Personnel Development), 1949-1956 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - University of California - Slavic Studies - (Personnel Development), 1949-1956 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - University of California - Slavic Studies - Reports, 1947, 1953; 2 items (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - University of California - Torres-Rioseco, Arturo - (Brazilian Literature), 1943, 1945, 1947, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - California - Social Sciences, 205.S
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Agricultural Economics - (Internship Program), 1950-1964 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Agricultural Economics - Reprints, 1960, 1966; 2 items (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - History, 1945-1955, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - History, 1945-1955, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Soviet Economic Development, 1948-1953, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Tomasevic, Jozo - (Yugoslav Agriculture), 1950-1953, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Stanford University - Yacobson, Sergius - (Soviet Political Language), 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - University of California - Brown, Delmer and Bisson, T.A. - (Far Eastern Affairs), 1949-1951, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - University of California - Business and Economic Research - (Gordon, R.A.), 1945-1952 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - University of California - Enemy Alien Study - (Japanese-Americans, Dorothy S. Thomas), 1942 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - University of California - Enemy Alien Study - (Japanese-Americans, Dorothy S. Thomas), 1943-1956 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - University of California - Enemy Alien Study - (Japanese-Americans, Dorothy S. Thomas), 1943-1956 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - University of California - Enemy Alien Study - Annual Reports, 1942-1944; 2 items (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - University of California - Old Age Stduies, 1949-1958, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - University of California - Old Age Stduies, 1949-1958, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - California - Virus Studies, 205.V
    - (Virus Studies, Travel Grants), 1958, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 87)
- Hawaii, 1946-1963; 214; 1.2 Cubic Feet; 3 __Boxes __1.2 cubic feet
  Material is divided into two subseries: 214 D Natural Sciences 214 R Humanities and the arts
  - University of Hawaii - Hayes, Samuel P. - (Presidential Search), 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hawaii - Natural Sciences, 214.D
    - University of Hawaii - Agriculture - (Visiting Researcher), 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Hawaii - Agricultural Education - (Fellowships), 1958-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Hawaii - Marine Laboratory - (Equipment Purchases), 1953-1955, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Hawaii - Rosenberg, Morton M. - (Travel Grant, Agriculture), 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii - Humanities and Arts, 214.R
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts - Chinese Painting - (Ecke, Gustav and Bety), 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts - Far Eastern Studies - (Kerr, George H.), 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts - Griffing, Robert P. - (Korean Art), 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University of Hawaii - Chong, Lily P.H. - (Chinese Literature), 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - University of Hawaii - Drama - (Translations), 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - University of Hawaii - Drama - Ernst, Earle - (Japanese Drama), 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - University of Hawaii - Music - (Oriental) - (Smith, Barbara B.), 1955-1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - University of Hawaii - Pacific Island Studies, 1946-1949, 1951-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of Hawaii - Pacific Island Studies, 1946-1949, 1951-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Hawaii - Pacific Island Studies - White, John Albert, 1952, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University of Hawaii - Philosophy - (Conferences), 1947-1952, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University of Hawaii - Philosophy Matson, Wallace "Report on Second East-West Philosophers' conference" June 20 - July 28, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - University of Hawaii - Philosophy Journal - (Philosophy East and West), 1949-1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - University of Hawaii - Stasack, Edward A. - (Fijian and Samoan Art), 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - University of Hawaii - Uyehara, Yukuo - (Japanese Literature), 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Illinois, 1931-1963; 216; 2.8 Cubic Feet; 7 __Boxes __2.8 cubic feet
  Material divided into 4 subseries: 216 A Medical Sciences 216 D Natural Sciences 216 R Humanities and the arts 216 S Social Sciences
  - University of Chicago - German University Project - (Faculty Exchange), 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago - German University Project - (Faculty Exchange), 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago - Student Exchange Study - (Taba, Hilda), 1950-1951, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Illinois - Medical Sciences, 216.A
    - University of Chicago - Psychotherapy - (James G. Miller, Carl R. Rogers), 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Chicago - Psychotherapy - (James G. Miller, Carl R. Rogers), 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Chicago - Psychotherapy - (James G. Miller, Carl R. Rogers), 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Chicago - Psychotherapy - (James G. Miller, Carl R. Rogers), 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Chicago - Psychotherapy - (James G. Miller, Carl R. Rogers), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Illinois - Natural Sciences, 216.D
    - Northwestern University - Genetics - (Drosophila Study, George H. Mickey), 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Northwestern University - Genetics - Protein Chemistry - (Klotz, I.M.), 1942, 1945-1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Northwestern University - Genetics - Protein Chemistry - (Klotz, I.M.), 1942, 1945-1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - University of Chicago - Bacteriology and Genetics - (Seminar Attendance) - (Leo Szilard, Salvador Luria), 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - University of Chicago - Biology Teaching Conference - (Weiss, Paul), 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of Chicago - Meteorite Studies - (Brown, Harrison), 1949-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Chicago - Nervous System Conference - (Weiss, Paul), 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Illinois - Humanities and Arts, 216.R
    - University of Chicago - Central American Studies, 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - University of Chicago - Humanities Development - (Geoffrey Tillotson, Visiting Professor), 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - University of Chicago - Humanities - Reports, 1931-1933; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - University of Chicago - Philology - (Buck, Carl D.), 1929-1936, 1939-1940, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - University of Chicago - Philosophy - (Morris, Charles William), 1942-1951 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - University of Chicago - Philosophy - (Morris, Charles William), 1952-1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - University of Chicago - Waples, Donald - (European Library Study), 1934-1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - University of Illinois - Radio - (Educational Broadcasters' Conference), 1948-1952, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - University of Illinois - Radio - (Educational Broadcasters' Conference), 1948-1952, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - University of Illinois - Radio - Reports, 1949; 2 Items (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Illinois - Social Sciences, 216.S
    - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics - (University of Chicago), 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics - (University of Chicago), 1948-1954 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics - (University of Chicago), 1948-1954 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics - (University of Chicago), 1948-1954 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics - Koopmans, Tjalling C. - (Travel Grant), 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Northwestern University - Brozen Yale - (Economic Implications of Technological Change), 1949-1952, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - University of Chicago - Aging Studies - (Ernest W. Burgess, Robert J. Havighurst), 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - University of Chicago - Aging Studies - (Ernest W. Burgess, Robert J. Havighurst), 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - University of Chicago - Agricultural Economics - (Theodore W. Schultz, D. Gale Johnson), 1943-1949 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - University of Chicago - Agricultural Economics - (Theodore W. Schultz, D. Gale Johnson), 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - University of Chicago - Agricultural Economics - Reports, 1949-1951; 7 Items (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - University of Chicago - Atomic Energy - (Commercial Uses), 1945-1951 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - University of Chicago - Atomic Energy - (Commercial Uses), 1945-1951 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - University of Chicago - Communications - (Voting Pattern Study), 1948-1954, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - University of Chicago - Communications - (Voting Pattern Study), 1948-1954, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - University of Chicago - Communications - Progress Report, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - University of Chicago - Communications - Economic History - (Hamilton, Earl J.) - (John Law Study), 1948-1952, 1954-1957 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - University of Chicago - Industrialism - (Nef, John U.), 1953-1961 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - University of Chicago - Production Study - (Douglas, Paul H.), 1948-1952, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - University of Chicago - Race Relations - (Wirth, Louis), 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - University of Chicago - Race Relations - (Wirth, Louis), 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - University of Chicago - Sauermann, Heinz - (Visiting Scholar, Economics), 1949-1951, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - University of Chicago - Sears, Roebuck History - (Emmet, Boris), 1945-1951 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Massachusetts, 1945-1958; 224; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  Material arranged in natural sciences subseries - 5 folders.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biology, 1947-1953, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biology - Proposal and Report, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Protein Chemistry - (Scotchard, George), 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Protein Chemistry - (Scotchard, George), 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Protein Chemistry - (Scotchard, George), 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts - Natural Sciences, 1945-1958; 224.D; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biology, 1947-1953, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biology - Proposal and Report, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Protein Chemistry - (Scotchard, George), 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Protein Chemistry - (Scotchard, George), 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Protein Chemistry - (Scotchard, George), 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minnesota, 1942-1960; 226; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  Material arranged in one subseries: 226 S Social Sciences
  - Minnesota - Social Sciences, 1942-1960; 226.S; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
    - University of Minnesota - Industrial Relations (Center), 1944-1952, 1955, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Minnesota - Industrial Relations (Center), 1944-1952, 1955, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Minnesota - Industrial Relations (Center), 1944-1952, 1955, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Minnesota - Intergovernmental Relations, 1945-1952, 1954-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Minnesota - Intergovernmental Relations, 1945-1952, 1954-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Minnesota - Intergovernmental Relations, 1945-1952, 1954-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Minnesota - Postwar Settlement - (Prarie Region), 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Mississippi, 1945-1949; 227; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  The material in this series is school health reports.
  - Nutrition - School Health Service - Reports, 1945-1949; 7 Items (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Nutrition - School Health Service - Reports, 1945-1949; 7 Items (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Missouri, 1940-1960; 228; 0.8 Cubic Feet; 2 __Boxes __0.8 cubic feet
  One subseries: 228 D Natural Sciences and agriculture
  - Missouri - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1940-1960; 228.D; 2 __Boxes __0.8 cubic feet
    - Washington University - Botany - (Barry Commoner, Plant Physiology and Biochemistry), 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Washington University - Botany - (Barry Commoner, Plant Physiology and Biochemistry), 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Washington University - Botany - (Barry Commoner, Plant Physiology and Biochemistry), 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Washington University - Botany - (Barry Commoner, Plant Physiology and Biochemistry), 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Washington University - Botany - Reprints, 1948-1956; 21 Items (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Washington University -Cyclotron, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Washington University -Cyclotron, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Washington University -Cyclotron, 1940-1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Washington University -Cyclotron, 1940-1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Washington University - Genetics - (Harrison D. Stalker, Hampton L. Carson), 1950-1954 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- New York, 1948-1950; 235; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  One folder on Physiology
  One subseries: 235 A Medical Sciences
  - New York - Medical Sciences, 1948-1950; 235.A; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
    - Long Island College of Medicine - Physiology - (Brooks, Chandler M.), 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- North Carolina, 1948-1966; 236; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  2 subseries as follows: 236 D Natural Sciences 236 R Humanities and arts
  - North Carolina - Natural Sciences, 236.D
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1948-1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics - Reports, 1948-1957; 7 Items (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - University of North Carolina - Genetics - Reports, 1948-1957; 7 Items (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina - Humanities and Arts, 236.R
    - University of North Carolina - Green Paul - (Oriental Drama), 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - University of North Carolina - Green, Paul - Report: "World Theatre Trip", 1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Ohio, 1946-1956; 238; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  One subseries: 238 A Medical Sciences
  - University of Cincinnati - Psychiatry - (Levine, Maurice), 1946-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University of Cincinnati - Psychiatry - (Levine, Maurice), 1946-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania, 1942-1960; 241; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  2 subseries as follows: 241 D Natural Sciences and agriculture 241 R Humanities and arts
  - Pennsylvania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 241.D
    - University of Pennsylvania - Biology - (Zoology, C. W. Metz), 1942-1948, 1952-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Biology - (Zoology, C. W. Metz), 1942-1948, 1952-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Biology - (Zoology, C. W. Metz), 1942-1948, 1952-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania - Humanities and Arts, 241.R
    - University of Pennsylvania - Indic Studies - (Linguistics, W. Norman Brown), 1947-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Philippines, 1951-1981; 242; 6 Cubic Feet; 35 __Boxes __6 cubic feet
  Material is largely agricultural files.
  This series is divided into the following 7 subseries: 242 A Medical Sciences 242 C Nursing 242 D Natural Sciences and agriculture 242 E Fellowships 242 R Humanities and arts 242 S Social Sciences 242 V Virus studies
  - National Science Development Board - Garcia, Paulino J. - (Travel Grant, Education), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University of the Philippines - Administrator - Scholar Program, 1963-1968, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University of the Philippines - (Agriculture) - (No Grant), 1962-1964, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University of the Philippines - Aragon, Potenciano R. - (Travel Grant, Public Health), 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University of the Philippines - Guzman, Virginia - (Travel Grant, Population), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University of the Philippines - Housing - (Faculty Home Construction), 1963-1969, 1974, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University of the Philippines - Housing - (Faculty Home Construction), 1963-1969, 1974, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University of the Philippines - Institute of Hygiene - Exchange Program, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University of the Philippines - Institute of Hygiene - Exchange Program, 1954-1960, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - University of the Philippines - Institute of Hygiene - Exchange Program, 1954-1960, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - University of the Philippines - Institute of Hygiene - Lara, Hilario - (Grant in Aid), 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University of the Philippines - International Center - (Construction), 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - University of the Philippines - Library - (Book Shipments), 1950-1953, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - University of the Philippines - Public Health - (Equipment Purchase), 1963-1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - University of the Philippines - Salcedo, Juan Sanchez - (Travel, Biochemistry and Nutrition), 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - University of the Philippines - Samson, Gregorio D. - (Grant in Aid, Hygiene and Public Health), 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - University of the Philippines - Sinco, Vincente G. - (Travel Grant, Conference Attendance), 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - University of the Philippines - Social Sciences and Humanities Center - (Equipment), 1966-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - University of the Philippines - Utility Systems Survey - (Campus Construction), 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - University of the Philippines - Valenzuela, Victor C. - (Travel Grant, Public Health), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - University of the Philippines -Yap, Paz Y. (Travel Grant, Testing), 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Salcedo, Juan - (Workshop Attendance), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - University of the Philippines - Anatomy - Request, 1968 (Box 001L, Folder 4)
  - University of the Philippines - (Department of Medicine) - (Equipment Purchase), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - University of the Philippines - Anatomy - (Department of) - (Equipment Purchase), 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - University of the Philippines - Bayani - Sioson, Pelagia S. - (Travel Grant, Biochemistry), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - University of the Philippines - Cabrera, Benjamin D. - (Travel Grant, Parasitology), 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - University of the Philippines - Campos, Paulo C. - (Travel Grant, Public Health), 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - University of the Philippines - Cytogenetics - (Dauis - Lawas, Domiciana), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - University of the Philippines - Dauis - Lawas, Domiciana - (Travel Grant, Pediatrics), 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - University of the Philippines - Eye Research Institute - (Equipment Research), 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - University of the Philippines - Guzman, Santiago V. - (Travel Grant, Physiology), 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - University of the Philippines - Histochemistry - (Tangeo, Oscar M.), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - University of the Philippines - Physiology - (Equipment Purchase), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - University of the Philippines - Physiology - Graduate program, 1963-1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - University of the Philippines - Tangco, Ambrosio F. - (Conference Attendance), 1964-1965, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - University of the Philippines - Vincente, Rustico - (Grant in Aid, Medical Electronics), 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - University of the Philippines - Visits, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - University of the Philippines - Crispino, Juana Basuel - (Travel, Nursing Centers), 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - University of the Philippines - Lara, Alma F. - (Travel, Nursing Centers), 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - University of the Philippines - Mangay - Maglacas, Amelia - (Rural Health Nursing), 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - University of the Philippines - Agriculture - List of Supplies, 1956 (Box 001L, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture - Marales, Marta T. - (Travel Grant, Potato Breeding), 1965, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Agriculture - Soils - (Bureau of) - (Equipment Purchase), 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)